Guide to the Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Atlantic Philanthropies Archives, 1982-2017.
8540
Atlantic Philanthropies (Organization).
2000 cubic feet.
926 gigabytes.
1.5 terabytes.
Grant files,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
This collection includes the corporate and grant making records of The Atlantic Philanthropies as well as the business records of many of the executives and program officers. The collection includes paper and electronic files.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
The Atlantic Philanthropies were founded by entrepreneur Charles F. ("Chuck") Feeney, a member of the Cornell University Class of 1956. Feeney, whose fortune stemmed from Duty Free Shoppers, decided in 1982 to devote his wealth to creating opportunity for others. Feeney's commitment to Giving While Living, the belief that people of wealth should use it to better the world during their lifetimes, has influenced Atlantic's grant making choices as well as the decision to limit Atlantic's life to a fixed term. The Atlantic Philanthropies will make final grants by December 31, 2016 and plans to close its doors in 2020, by which time nearly $8 billion will have been invested in people, programs, and capital projects around the world. Grant awards to Cornell University total nearly $1 billion from 1982 through 2016.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
This collection includes the corporate and grant making records of The Atlantic Philanthropies as well as the business records of many of the executives and program officers. The collection includes paper and electronic files.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Atlantic Philanthropies (Organization).; Feeney, Chuck, 1931-
Subjects:
Charity organization.; Endowments.; Charities.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing.
SERIES LIST
Series IV. Grant Files
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IV: Grant Files
  - Subseries E: Great Britian grant files, 1974-2011
    Files for grants the Atlantic Philanthropies made in Great Britain.
    Subseries arranged alphabetically into subseries by grantee.
    Great Britain
    - Acre, 1990-1993; ACRE (Organisation)
      ACRE (Organisation)
      Community Development and Civic Engagement
      Rural Development
      Civic Participation and Civil Society
      - #7010 (#90-16). Action with Communities in Rural England (ACRE). Fundraising development program, 1990-1993 (Box 184, Folder 3)
    - Action Group for Irish Youth, 1991-1996; Action Group for Irish Youth (Great Britain)
      Action Group for Irish Youth (Great Britain)
      - #7071 (#91-55). Promoting the interest and welfare of young Irish people in London, 1991-1994 (Box 184, Folder 4)
        Youth Development (Non-School-Based)
        Youth Development Services
      - #7170 (#93-3). Database on Irish users of welfare services in Britain, 1993-1995 (Box 184, Folder 5)
      - #7315 (#95-24). Develop, extend, and independently manage SIS database, 1994-1996 (Box 184, Folder 6)
        Equality, Rights, and Justice
        Access restrictions apply.
    - Almeida Theatre Company Limited, 1994-2005; Almeida Theatre (London, England)
      Almeida Theatre (London, England)
      Miscellaneous
      Performing Arts
      Cultural Awareness
      - #8748. Theatre refurbishment. Key documents, 2001 (Box 184, Folder 7)
      - Almeida Theatre Company Limited, 1994, 2000-2005 (Box 184, Folder 8-10)
    - Amber Foundation, 1994-2003
      Amber Foundation
      - #9261. Expansion plan, 2001, 2003 (Box 184, Folder 11)
        Equal Opportunity in Education
        Substance Abuse Prevention
      - #9261. Expansion plan. Key documents, 2002-2003 (Box 184, Folder 12)
      - Amber Foundation. Reports, 2001, 2002 (Box 184, Folder 13)
      - Amber Foundation. Publications, 1994-1995, 2000, 2001, 2003 (Box 184, Folder 14)
        - ACF, 2003-07-02; FD-944 (Box 184, Folder 14)
          floppy disk
      - Amber Project. Business plans, reports, supplemental materials, 2001-2003 (Box 184, Folder 15)
        - Amber Foundation Report, FD-945 (Box 184, Folder 15)
    - Amber Trust, 2000
      Amber Trust
      Nonprofit Sector/Voluntarism/Philanthropy
      Foundations
      - #8081 (#00-88). Monies for Michael Gwinnell and family to disburse, 2000 (Box 184, Folder 16)
        Harvey Dale discretionary grant. Not on FLUXX
    - ARCS (UK) LimitedInside Out Trust, 2003-2008; ARCS (UK) Limited; Inside Out Trust
      ARCS (UK) Limited
      Inside Out Trust
      - #12246. Independent evaluation. Key documents, 2003-2004 (Box 184, Folder 17)
      - #12246. Independent evaluation, 2003-2008 (Box 184, Folder 18)
        Dublin office cabinet file 9/2/14
    - Association of Charitable Foundations, 1997-2008
      Association of Charitable Foundations
      - #10296. Associate Membership of the Association of Charitable Foundations. #12075. Core Staffing, 2002, 2004-2005 (Box 184, Folder 19)
      - #12075. Association membership, 2002-2006, 2008 (Box 184, Folder 20)
        Dublin office cabinet file 23/14
      - #12075. Core staffing. Key documents, 2003 (Box 184, Folder 21)
      - Association of Charitable Foundations, 1997, 1999-2007 (Box 184, Folder 22-23)
    - Aston UniversityCentre for Voluntary Action Research, 1999-2004; University of Aston in Birmingham
      University of Aston in Birmingham
      Centre for Voluntary Action Research (Great Britain)
      - #10050. Voluntary sector capacity building program, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 184, Folder 24)
        Effective Nonprofits and Philanthropy
        University
        Voluntarism
      - #10050. Voluntary sector capacity building program. Key documents, 2001-2004 (Box 184, Folder 25)
      - Centre for Voluntary Action Research. Proposals and supplemental materials, 1999-2002 (Box 184, Folder 26)
      - Centre for Voluntary Action Research. Confidential report, 2003-01-27 (Box 184, Folder 27)
      - Centre for Voluntary Action Research. Final reports, 2003 (Box 184, Folder 28)
      - Centre for Voluntary Action Research. Reports and supplemental material, 2000-2001 (Box 184, Folder 29)
      - Centre for Voluntary Action Research. Reports and correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 185, Folder 1-2)
      - Centre for Voluntary Action Research. Literature review, 2003-03-13 (Box 185, Folder 3)
    - Birkbeck CollegeUniversity of London, 2001-2007; Birkbeck College; University of London
      Birkbeck College
      University of London
      Higher Education
      Educational Management
      Economic Development
      - #10913. Research study of benefits of part time study, 2001-2007 (Box 185, Folder 4-5)
      - #10913. Research study of benefits of part time study (BBK magazine), December 2002 and Summer 2005 (Box 26, Folder 12)
        BBK magazine, issues 13 (December 2002) and 18 (Summer 2005)
      - #10913. Research study of benefits of part time study. Key documents, 2002 (Box 185, Folder 6)
    - Brandon Centre, 1997-2011; Brandon Centre (Organization)
      Brandon Centre (Organization)
      - #10604. Multisystemic therapy for young offenders, 2001-2005 (Box 185, Folder 7)
        Youth Development (Non-School Based)
        Mental Health Care
        Legal Aid
      - #13022. Multi-systemic therapy for young offenders - extension to current grant, 2004, 2006-2007, 2011 (Box 185, Folder 8)
        Republic of Ireland
        Children and Youth
        Services for Offenders
      - #13022. Multi-systemic therapy for young offenders - extension to current grant, 1997-1998, 2003-2007 (Box 185, Folder 9-10)
    - British Institute of Human Rights, 2002-2007
      British Institute of Human Rights
      - #12583. Building organizational capacity, 2002, 2004-2006 (Box 185, Folder 11)
        Dublin office audit file.
        Great Britain. Equality and Human Rights Commission
        Reconciliation and Human Rights
        Race and Intergroup Relations
      - #12583. Building organizational capacity. Key documents, 2002-2004 (Box 185, Folder 12)
      - #12583. Â N 28/7/3 Building organizational capacity. Establishment of CEHR, 2004-2007 (Box 185, Folder 13-14)
      - Making Sense of Human Rights (annual reviews), 2004-2006 (Box 185, Folder 15)
        Includes Annual Review 2004 and 2005-2006; "Support" brochure
      - Guides, 2006 (Box 185, Folder 16)
      - BIHR Brief. Newsletters, 2005-2007 (Box 185, Folder 17)
      - Reports and general information, 2006-2007 (Box 185, Folder 18)
    - Cambridge Foundation, 1997-2009; University of Cambridge
      University of Cambridge
      - Cambridge - major gifts, 1999-09, 1999-11 (Box 184, Folder 1)
        Dublin cabinet file 36/3/2. Contains emails and memorandum
      - Cambridge. English 2000, 1999-10-01 (Box 184, Folder 2)
        Dublin office cabinet file 36/3/2/5
      - #7820 (#99-29). Centre for Mathematical Sciences, 1998-2004 (Box 185, Folder 19-20)
        University of Cambridge. Centre for Mathematical Sciences
        Universities
        Mathematics
      - #7820 (#99-29.) Centre for Mathematical Studies, 1999 (Box 185, Folder 21)
        Dublin office cabinet file (36/3/2/1)
      - #7878. Library development programme and key documents, 1999-2003 (Box 185, Folder 22)
        Cambridge University Library
        Academic Libraries
        Law Libraries
      - #7878 (#99-85.) Southwest corner library extension, 1999-2003 (Box 185, Folder 23)
        Dublin office cabinet file (36/3/2/3)
      - #7878. Cambridge University. South West corner phase of library (reports), 2000-2002 (Box 186, Folder 1)
      - #7955 (#99-160). University of Cambridge Cancer Research UK, 1998-2009 (Box 186, Folder 2-4)
        Cambridge Research Institute (Great Britain)
        Imperial Cancer Research Fund (Great Britain)
        Biomedical Research
        Health
        Cancers
      - #7955 (#99-160). University of Cambridge Cancer Research UK. Key documents, 1999-2001, 2003-2004 (Box 186, Folder 5)
      - #7955 Cancer Research Collaboration with ICRF (Imperial Cancer Research Fund), 2001, 2003-2008 (Box 186, Folder 6)
        Dublin office cabinet file 36/3/2/6
      - #8034. College Based Access Initiatives, 1999-2003 (Box 186, Folder 7)
        Dublin office cabinet file (36/3/2/8 )
        College Preparation
      - #8034. Core support. College-based access initiatives. Key documents, 2000-2001, 2003 (Box 186, Folder 8)
      - #8034. Core support. Cambridge Access Initiatives. Correspondence and supplemental material, 1999-2003, 2005 (Box 186, Folder 9)
      - #8034. Core support. Cambridge Access Initiatives. Reports, 1997-2002 (Box 186, Folder 10-11)
      - #8034. Cambridge Access projects. Reports and supplemental materials, 2000-2003, 2005 (Box 186, Folder 12-13)
      - #9004. CIAO - Northern Schools Conference, 2001 (Box 186, Folder 14)
        University of Oxford
      - #9004. Oxford and Cambridge Northern Schools Conference, and key documents, 2000-2001 (Box 186, Folder 15)
      - #9306. English faculty building, 2001-2002, 2004 (Box 186, Folder 16)
        University of Cambridge. Faculty of English
        Social Sciences
      - #9306. English faculty building. Key documents, 2001-2004 (Box 186, Folder 17)
      - #9306. English faculty building, 2000-2004 (Box 186, Folder 18-19)
      - #10077. Cambridge Institute for Diabetes, Endocrinology, and Metabolism (CIDEM). Dublin file., 2001-2002, 2005-2007 (Box 186, Folder 20)
        Dublin office cabinet file 36/3/2/11
        Specialty Hospitals
        Endocrine, Nutritional and Metabolic Diseases
      - #10077. Cambridge Diabetes Institute, 2001-2008 (Box 186, Folder 21-22)
      - #10077. Cambridge Diabetes Institute. Key documents, 2001-2002 (Box 186, Folder 23)
      - Cambridge University - general, 1999-2001 (Box 186, Folder 24-25)
      - Oxford and Cambridge Northern Schools Conference, 1999-2000 (Box 186, Folder 26)
      - University of Cambridge. Loose reports, 2000 (Box 186, Folder 27)
    - Cambridge Rowing Trust, 1997-2003
      Cambridge Rowing Trust
      Rivers and Lakes
      - #7822 (#99-31.) Core costs, 1999 (Box 187, Folder 1)
        Dublin office cabinet file 36/3/2/2
      - #7822 (#99-31). Cambridge Rowing Lake operating and fundraising support, 1997-2003 (Box 187, Folder 2)
      - #7822 (#99-31). Cambridge Rowing Lake operating and fundraising support. Key documents, 1999-2000 (Box 187, Folder 3)
    - Carers National Association, 1991-1997; Carers' National Association (Great Britain)
      Carers' National Association (Great Britain)
      Aging
      Nursing Care
      Senior Services
      - # 7074 (#91-59) Funding to make up shortfall of regional offices in Belfast and Wales, 1991-1993, 1996-1997 (Box 187, Folder 4)
    - Centre for Crime and Justice Studies, 2002-2008; Centre for Crime and Justice Studies (Great Britain)
      Centre for Crime and Justice Studies (Great Britain)
      - #11743. Change: Extending Boundaries of Thinking About the Criminal Justice System. Key documents, 2003 (Box 187, Folder 5)
        Government and Public Administration
        Crime and Abuse
        Justice Rights
      - #12214. Whose Justice?, 2003-2007 (Box 187, Folder 6)
        Dublin office cabinet file 9/2/10
        Courts/Judicial Administration
        Due Process
        Correctional Facilities and Services
      - #12214. Whose Justice? Key documents, 2003-2004 (Box 187, Folder 7)
      - #12261. Change: Developing and Advocating Fresh Thinking and Policies on Crime. Key documents, 2003-2004 (Box 187, Folder 8)
      - #12261. Change - Developing and Advocating Fresh Thinking and Policies on Crime, 2003, 2006-2007 (Box 187, Folder 9)
        Dublin office cabinet file Cab. 7, Dr. 1B, 9/2/2011
      - Centre for Crime and Justice Studies (CCJS), 2002-2008 (Box 187, Folder 10-11)
    - Centrepoint Soho, 1991-1994
      Centrepoint Soho
      - #7075 (#91-60). Cinema advertisement, 1991-1992 (Box 187, Folder 12)
        Homeless Services
      - Centrepoint Soho. Personnel and training officer (not funded), 1991-1994 (Box 187, Folder 13)
    - Chalcs, 1994-2001; Chapeltown and Harehills Assisted Learning
      Chapeltown and Harehills Assisted Learning
      - #7277 (#94-48). Education program extension and evaluation, 1994-1996, 1998 (Box 187, Folder 14)
        Youth Development
        Program Expansion
        Operating Support
        Program Evaluation
      - CHALCS (Chapeltown and Harehills Assisted Learning Computer School), 1994-1999 (Box 187, Folder 15-17)
      - CHALCS. Performance report and associated materials, 2000-2001 (Box 187, Folder 18)
    - Charities Aid Foundation, 1992-2003
      Charities Aid Foundation
      - #7163 (#92-73). Committee for the promotion of an accrediting bureau for charities, 1992-1995, 1997-1998 (Box 187, Folder 19)
      - #9141. Charities Aid Foundation. Key documents., 2001 (Box 187, Folder 20)
        Philanthropy and Public Policy
        Social Entrepreneurship
      - #12219. Challenges for policy and practice in funding social enterprise activity - supplementary report. Key documents, 2003 (Box 187, Folder 21)
      - Charities Aid Foundation, 2000-2003 (Box 187, Folder 22-23)
    - Charities Evaluation ServicesÂ (CES), 1992-2002; Charities Evaluation Services
      Charities Evaluation Services
      - Charities Evaluation Services, 1993, 1995-1997, 1999-2002 (Box 187, Folder 24-26)
        Folder contains reports, reviews, financial statements, and additional supplemental materials.
      - Charities Evaluation Services. 23/4. Part I, 1992-1999 (Box 187, Folder 27-29)
      - Charities Evaluation Services. 23/4. Part 2, 1999-2000 (Box 187, Folder 30)
    - Children's Express, 1995-2003; Children's Express (Organization)
      Children's Express (Organization)
      - #7453 (#96-78), #8405, #9606. Core support, 1996-2001, 2003 (Box 188, Folder 1)
        Youth community service
      - #7453. Core support. File 14/4, 1995-1999 (Box 188, Folder 2-3)
      - File 14/4. Part 1. Progress and funding report, 1999 (Box 188, Folder 4)
      - File 14/4 - Part 2, 1998-2000 (Box 188, Folder 5)
      - #9606. Core costs. Key documents, 1996-2003 (Box 188, Folder 6-7)
        Also contains materials for grant 8405.
      - Children's Express, 1996, 1998-2003 (Box 188, Folder 8-10)
      - Loose materials, 2000-2002 (Box 188, Folder 11)
        Folder contains Project Proposal, notes/updates, Annual Report Year 1, and Business Plan 2002-2006.
      - Program manual. Draft version, 2001 (Box 188, Folder 12)
      - Reports, 2001-04 (Box 188, Folder 13)
    - Churchill College Archives TrustUniversity of Cambridge, 1999-2006; Churchill College. Archives Centre; University of Cambridge
      Churchill College. Archives Centre
      Archives and Special Collections
      - #10079. Core funding- Churchill Archives Centre, 1999-2006 (Box 188, Folder 14-15)
      - #10079. Core funding Churchill Archives Centre, 2001, 2005 (Box 188, Folder 16)
      - #10079. Core funding- Churchill Archives Centre. Key documents, 2001-2004 (Box 188, Folder 17)
    - Community Foundation Network, 1994-2005; Community Foundation Network (Great Britain); UK Community Foundations
      Community Foundation Network was renamed the UK Community Foundations in 2013.
      Community Foundation Network (Great Britain)
      UK Community Foundations
      - #7670 (#98-37). Development and training programs, 23/2/1/1, 1998-2000, 1994, 1996-2000 (Box 188, Folder 18-19)
        Nonprofit Management
        Leadership Development
      - #8254. Network development, 2001, 2003-2004 (Box 188, Folder 20)
        Citizen Coalitions
      - #8254. Network development. Key documents, 1998, 2000-2002 (Box 188, Folder 21)
      - Community Foundation Network. Folder 1, 2000-2003 (Box 188, Folder 22)
      - Community Foundation Network. Folder 2, 1999-2000, 2003-2004 (Box 189, Folder 1)
      - Community Foundation Network. Folder 3, 2000-2005 (Box 189, Folder 2-4)
    - Community Youth Leadership Project, 2003
      Community Youth Leadership Project
      - Community Youth Leadership Project, 2003 (Box 189, Folder 5)
    - ContinYou, 1991-2005; ContinYou (Organization)
      Organization was previously known as the Community Education Development Centre (CEDC) prior to its merger with Education Extra in 2003.
      ContinYou (Organization)
      - #7342 (#95-51). SHARE Innovative Project, 1994-1998, 2001 (Box 189, Folder 6)
        Community Education Development Centre (Organization)
        Pre-Collegiate Education and Teacher Development
        Parent Education
        Elementary School Education
        Parent-Teacher Groups
      - #10588. SHARE and Parents in the Community, 2002, 2005 (Box 189, Folder 7)
        Early Childhood Development
        Early Childhood Education
      - #10588. SHARE and Parents in the Community. Key documents, 2002-2003 (Box 189, Folder 8)
      - CEDC (Community Education Development Centre), 2000-2003 (Box 189, Folder 9-10)
      - ContinYou, 2000-2004 (Box 189, Folder 11)
      - Correspondence and financial information, 1991-1994 (Box 189, Folder 12)
      - CEDC - loose materials, 2001-2003 (Box 189, Folder 13)
        Folder contains annual reviews, discussion paper, and correspondence.
      - Publications for SHARE program, 1997, 1999-2002 (Box 189, Folder 14)
      - Publications. Folder 1, 1999-2000 (Box 189, Folder 15)
      - Publications. Folder 2, 1999-2001 (Box 189, Folder 16)
      - SHARE and Parents in the Community promotional materials., 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 16)
        Includes promotional plastic bag
        - Making time for rhyme, 2002-2003; CD-5396 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Corpus Christi CollegeUniversity of Cambridge, 1987-2011; Corpus Christi College (University of Cambridge); University of Cambridge
      Corpus Christi College (University of Cambridge)
      - #7199 (#93-33a). Support for Development Office, 1993-1997 (Box 189, Folder 17)
        Undergraduate Colleges
      - #7199 (#93-33b). Robert Beldam Building in Bene't Court, 1993-1995 (Box 189, Folder 18)
      - #7199. Development Office/Beldam (Bene't) Building. Key documents, 1993-1998 (Box 189, Folder 19)
      - #7401 (#96-26); #7499 (#97-27). Parker Library, 1996-1997 (Box 189, Folder 20)
        Corpus Christi College (University of Cambridge). Library
      - #7499 (#97-27), #7821 (#99-30), #10293. Parker Library project. Key documents, 1996-2000, 2002 (Box 189, Folder 21)
      - #7543 (#97-70). CCCC School Teacher Fellow Commoners, 1994, 1997-2004 (Box 190, Folder 1-2)
      - #7543 (#97-70). School teacher fellow commoner program, 1997, 2003 (Box 190, Folder 3)
      - #7543 (#97-70). CCCC School Teacher Fellow Commoners. Key documents, 1997-1999 (Box 190, Folder 4)
      - #7821 (#99-30). Parker Library project. Key documents, 1999-2000 (Box 190, Folder 5)
      - #7821 (#99-30). Parker Library (2001-, 2001-2006, 2008, 2011 (Box 190, Folder 6-7)
        Fodler contains report for grant #11062 (Womankind Worldwide)
      - Bene't Court 1997/1998, 1997 (Box 190, Folder 8)
      - Cambridge University. Corpus Christi College, 1990-1991, 1993, 1996-1997, 1999, 2003 (Box 190, Folder 9)
      - Cambridge University. Corpus Christi College, 1993-1995 (Box 190, Folder 10)
      - CCCC Development Office, 1997/1998/1999, 1987, 1996-1999 (Box 190, Folder 11)
      - CCCC Development Office, 2000, 1997, 1999-2001 (Box 190, Folder 12)
      - CCCC general, 1994-1999, 1994-1999 (Box 190, Folder 13)
      - CCCC general, 2000, 1999-2003 (Box 190, Folder 14)
      - Corpus Christi general (June 2003-, 2003-2004 (Box 190, Folder 15)
      - CCCC Parker Library digitization agreement, 1999-2000 (Box 190, Folder 16)
      - CCCC Parker Library project, 1995-1998, 1994-1998 (Box 190, Folder 17)
      - CCCC Parker Library project. Submission to the Heritage Lottery Fund. 8 September 1998, 1998 (Box 190, Folder 18)
      - CCCC Parker Library project, 1999, 1993, 1999 (Box 190, Folder 19-20)
      - CCCC Parker Library project, 2000, 1998-2000, 2004-2005 (Box 190, Folder 21-22)
        Folder 21 contains correspondence and report for grant #7821.
      - CCCC Parker Library project, 2001, 1999-2003 (Box 190, Folder 23)
    - Council for Advancement and Support of Education (Europe), 2001-2006; Council for Advancement and Support of Education
      Council for Advancement and Support of Education
      - #9303. CASE Europe. Spring Institute of Fundraising, 2001, 2003, 2006 (Box 191, Folder 1)
      - #9513. Strategic planning grant, 2001 (Box 191, Folder 2)
        International Development
      - #10692. CASE Europe. Core funding, 2002-2004, 2006 (Box 191, Folder 3)
    - Council for Assisting Refugee Academics (CARA), 1998-2005; Council for Assisting Refugee Academics
      Council for Assisting Refugee Academics
      - #11807. Core support. Key documents, 2003 (Box 191, Folder 4)
        Right to Free Movement and Asylum
      - Council for Assisting Refugee Academics - CARA, 1998-1999, 2001-2005 (Box 191, Folder 5-8)
    - Crime Reduction Initiatives, 2000-2003
      Crime Reduction Initiatives
      - #8870. CDHA - Hyde launch, 2001-2002 (Box 191, Folder 9)
      - #8870. Promoting the involvement of young people in planning services across Sussex. Key documents, 2000-2001 (Box 191, Folder 10)
      - #8870. Promoting the involvement of young people in planning services in Sussex. The Atlantic Philanthropies final report, 2003-12 (Box 191, Folder 11)
      - Crime Reduction Initiatives. Supplemental materials and correspondence, 2000-2003 (Box 191, Folder 12)
      - Crime Reduction Initiatives. Supplemental materials, 2000-2003 (Box 191, Folder 13-14)
        - CRI: mind the gap, 2002; DVD-3373 (Box 191, Folder 13)
          DVD
    - Dartington Hall Trust, 1998-2004; Dartington Social Research Unit